A trailblazing leader in government,
business, and philanthropy.
>> A former presidential advisor to Donald
Trump, Dina Powell McCormick joined Meta
Platforms as president and vice
chairwoman.
>> She'll help lead the company's massive
AI expansion [music] including data
centers, investments, and global
partnerships.
>> Powell McCormick's background is exactly
where Meta's new bottlenecks [music]
are.
>> There is a transformation in humanity
coming. Nothing can stop that now with
this technology. 3.5 billion people
every [music] day are on Meta. I think
we all know that the next 3 years could
be the whole game.
>> Women are the secret sauce.
>> [laughter]
>> How about that?
>> Please welcome Dina Powell McCormick.
>> [music]
>> See you. Thanks for coming out.
Hey, good to
All right, good to see you.
How are you?
>> Dina, thank you for being here.
Um
you know, we were just finishing up a
conversation with Satya about how do we
tell the story
about the benefit of data centers and
what they're doing to communities and
why they're actually net economically
positive.
And I know you so I'm going to get right
into it cuz I know you actually have a
video on this. Do you want to just start
with your video? Would that be okay?
>> That'd be great. I mean, I just want to
say so psyched to be at the All-In
Summit. First time to speak. And as long
as this episode and panel gets way more
listeners and views than Senator
McCormick's did when he came on, I'll be
very, very happy with that. So now we
can now we can roll the tape. No
competition.
>> Good. We'll put it on Polymarket.
Let's watch the video.
>> [music]
>> Richmond Parish was the place that
opportunity forgot about.
>> [music]
>> I've grown up here my whole life.
And I've seen a lot of people move away
looking for work, including my son.
>> [music]
>> What you were hearing a lot lately was,
"There's nothing here for us anymore."
>> We knew that having [music] a data
center would give us an industry here
that we haven't had before. That's a
huge [music] investment in our
community.
>> We started this business simply because
Meta [music] was coming.
>> We thought [music] we had hit it big
when we got to cater for 40 people. Now
we do 400 a week.
>> [music]
>> Since Meta came to town, we've hired
more employees.
>> A multi-billion dollar capital
investment like the one that [music]
Meta is making in Richland Parish is
it was transformative. [music]
It's extremely exciting to attract and
retain quality teachers.
>> [music]
>> So when I first got the news about the
bonus, it was jaw-dropping. My mouth was
literally wide open.
>> We're not [music] in it for the money.
We're teachers because it's in our
heart. But the bonus has been extremely
helpful.
>> [music]
>> With the investment that Meta has made
in our community,
now we can [music] do a better job of
taking care of our own.
>> Yeah, I do feel a lot of hope for the
future of my students. [music] It gives
them the opportunity that they never
thought that they would have.
>> And I would say one of the biggest
things is people [music] coming back
home.
>> You know, [music] the future is
happening here and happening now.
>> [applause]
>> You have some folks from the video here?
>> I do.
>> Should we bring them out?
>> Come on out. Sheldon and Susan, we have
superintendent [music]
from that video, the superintendent in
Richland Parish.
>> [music]
>> Thanks for joining us.
>> Pleasure. [music]
>> Hi, sir.
>> Hi.
>> Thanks for joining us.
>> Hi, Sheldon.
>> How are you?
>> Come on down.
>> Good to meet you. How are you?
Thank you for being here.
>> Thanks for having us.
>> You want to do an introduction?
>> Sure. What an honor. It's an honor uh
for me to be here with Sheldon and
Susan.
Uh we spent a lot of time in Louisiana.
It's our largest data center investment
uh for Meta. And I've been with them in
Louisiana. And what is remarkable to me
is just the leadership that frankly the
governor has shown. Susan is the
commerce secretary for Louisiana, the
economic development um secretary. And
Sheldon uh who I'm going to let him
speak for himself, but he is such an
inspirational figure there. And he is
the one that realized that because of
our investment
the tax surplus would go straight to
teachers. And maybe you can talk just a
little bit about that.
>> Yes, so it's great to be here. Um I just
think back to my first interaction with
Meta. Uh
it was in the summer of 2024.
And um
it was at our local community college.
And I just remember after the meeting
getting in my car and uh it's hot in
Louisiana. So I turned the air on. And I
just sat there and I said,
"The game has changed." Um this is going
to give our parish an opportunity to do
something that it's never been able to
do. So, when the
groundbreaking ceremony happened in
December of 2024,
um I could immediately start to see the
increase in our sales tax collections.
Um there are six taxing entities in our
parish. The Richland Parish School Board
collects 51% of the taxes for the
district. Um so, I was able to see the
sales tax collections go from
5%, 10%, which is normal for a school
system,
to about 60%
and at that time the number of workers
at the data center site increased. Um
those collections peaked at about 260%.
That's an increase in sales tax
collections.
Um and so, we have a 1 cent and a 1/2
cent sales tax that's dedicated to
employee salaries. And so, we're
announcing these sales tax increases at
our school board meetings and we're
educators, so people can do the math.
>> [laughter]
>> They start to figure out this is going
to translate into a larger sales tax
check, which directly goes into our
salaries. So,
in December of 2025, we gave out a 1/2
cent sales tax check. That check doubled
from the previous year. So, it went from
roughly about $4,000 to about $8,000,
but we hadn't seen a full year of spiked
increases in sales tax collections. That
happened this past June. Uh so, our
certified employees received an increase
of about $40,000
in their sales tax check.
>> check?
>> They got a $50,000 check.
>> Wow.
>> [applause]
>> So, the check the previous year was
$10,000.
So, if you take that December increase
and the June increase, it was a a net of
about $45,000
for our teachers.
>> Did they all cuz the reason Tina and I
were talking about this panel, and
everyone hates data centers.
They poll -80 in the United States. And
Tina was telling me the story, and I was
like, we should tell this story because
it is unbelievable. Did the teachers and
the community have this negative
sentiment about data centers before?
Were they all we hate data centers, we
don't want them here? Or was that before
this wave happened, and the community
didn't really kind of pay much attention
to it?
>> I think initially there was the unknown.
Um and we are
we are the beginning. We're a starting
point. There was no reference for us to
to access. We couldn't say, okay, well,
when the last time When was the last
time we had a $50 capital investment in
our schools? [laughter]
So, how do we handle that?
So, yeah, we're you know, a few million
dollars, that's that's that's huge for
us. So, um
there was there was
anxious thoughts. Um I think Meta has
done an excellent job of informing us
and educating us. And that's going to
have to continue to happen. Oftentimes,
this communication is not about the most
informed person in the community, it's
about the least informed person in the
community. So, we're working to make
sure that we continue to get that
positive message out about the good
things that are happening because there
are a lot of good things that are
happening in our parish.
>> Yeah, I think it to the superintendent's
point, um Louisiana was a little bit
late to the data center game, which has
actually worked remarkably well to our
benefit in that the the meta investment
was the first one in the state.
Um and because of the partnership, the
way um we negotiated the deal, I call it
a a partnership not a negotiation
frankly all all along, um the community
when we first brought the idea even
prior to you knowing superintendent, um
the community wasn't apprehensive
because there was a great deal of
unknown. Now, keep in mind this was now
about 20 months ago is when we started
the conversation there. Um so so the the
chatter wasn't as much as it is now, but
you're talking about a community that
was really starved for opportunity. As
you saw in the video, you know, we had
lost population. Uh
the average wages in Richland Parish
were roughly 36, 38,000 dollars a year
prior to this investment. So um the data
center went to a place in Louisiana, you
know, Mississippi Delta Parish that was
Mississippi River Delta obviously. It
was It was longing for this opportunity.
And we got ahead of that and I think we
got ahead of that very wisely in the way
we um addressed both the concerns, the
impact on the community, um the good
impact on the community, and the natural
resources, and all the things we're
hearing, right?
>> In a In a weird way then all of this
noise is actually somewhat beneficial in
the sense that you may just want to go
to DNA and say, "We'll just take all
your data centers."
>> [laughter]
>> Cuz you can't I mean I mean quite
honestly
>> I think our governor would actually say
that.
>> this continuous change in the in the
earnings potential of
normal average Americans.
>> Yeah, we the governor just signed an
executive order a few months ago
creating a framework for us under which
we will engage with large load users,
right? And the privilege that it gives
us now is we get to be choosy, right? We
We have a a sales tax exemption, which
is critical to be able to land an
investment of this size and this scale,
but now we get to really court who our
partners are going to be, and the
governor claims it all the time that
meta really was the prototype for us and
it set a very high standard. And that's
now the standard we're going to follow.
We are not one of those states who is
saying no. We are one of those states
that are saying yes and.
>> Yeah, so
maybe you could help us with
>> [applause]
>> it's pretty clear the economic case for
you know, building and growing and
creating jobs.
Take us through the list of valid
concerns communities have. One of them's
pollution. I'm not sure if this is
running off of gas or if it's all solar
and renewables, increased electricity
cost, water, closed loop versus
non-closed loop, noise pollution and
aesthetics. These buildings are awfully
ugly and typically as created. Did any
of those apply? Did you get any of that
feedback from the community?
>> Our journalist.
>> What's that?
>> No, no, no. Actually it's not
journalism. Actually what it is is it's
facts. Facts. These are the facts of the
the people Hold on, I'll finish.
These are the facts that community
members have valid concerns about. There
are people who have had data centers put
next to them that are polluting, that
are creating noise and there are valid
water concerns and there are communities
where their electricity went up. So I'm
asking a serious question based on
facts. I'm wondering if any of those
apply to you.
>> Yeah, Genie, you said this was going to
be easy. No, no, no.
Yeah, clearly, you know, we're all
people, right? We all hear, we all have
the same concerns.
Again, some of it was that we got very
lucky with the timing of all this
because those issues were addressed
before they became in the public forum
of issues. You know, number one, this
was farmland. This was agricultural
land. And early on in the conversations
with with the meta team,
they they made a decision to use a more
expensive but more efficient system that
actually uses less water than was you
being used on that land when it was
being farmed.
Right? It's not a statistic you hear
very often. The second piece about the
energy, clearly we're we're hearing it
across the board, but there are two
really critical components to this.
Number one is that Louisiana has
abundant natural gas. We have about
32,000 miles of natural gas pipelines in
Louisiana today, if we don't add another
mile. So, we have access to natural gas
everywhere.
But but in the in the relationship that
Meta created with Entergy, the the
energy provider there,
um from day one, before this was a an
executive order from the president or
even the governor, Meta paid for its own
generation. It paid for grid resilience.
It paid for grid upgrades. It paid for
storm costs. Louisiana has storm
assessments when we have hurricanes. It
happens every now and then. It's paying
for storm costs in a state where they
didn't operate, right? When these
hurricanes hit. So, it's actually taking
burdens off of the Louisiana consumer.
So, all those issues were issues, and
they were addressed with the original um
negotiated deal. And I will say, it's
really why it's become the prototype for
how we move forward with others.
>> this is a question for you. You used to
be the deputy national security advisor.
So, answer this maybe with just a bit of
that hat on.
I mean, Jason brings up valid concerns,
but then there's this data that is so
clear for you, but also for others. I
mean, you just heard from Satya.
Why is this misinformation campaign
winning so soundly in America?
What has happened? Like, what is going
on?
>> Well, I think first, the questions that
Jason raised are really legitimate
questions. And I think we start with a
premise that if a community doesn't want
one of our data centers, they get to
choose. They get to decide. But that we
actually have to upfront and way more
aggressively explain what our investment
and partnership means. And we have a
compact, a compact that Susan and and
Sheldon are describing. First, not just
pay for your own electricity. Make sure
that you're working to drive electricity
costs down. The second is the water
issue. It's very real in farmlands and
rural communities, but there's
absolutely now new technology, in fact
AI-driven technology, that makes you
able to actually increase water
consumption. The third is the teachers.
I'll be very honest, this was not our
idea. This actually happened because
this law
allows or in fact mandates that every
extra dollar of tax surplus goes
directly to the teachers. And the
superintendent was telling me things
that just are so remarkable. Used to
have a hard time recruiting teachers.
Now his phone is ringing off the hook
throughout Louisiana, teachers wanting
to come there, and this may end up being
the best school district in the entire
state. And now we have taken that
learning and we're investing in teachers
and first responders. And you saw of
course the economic development impact
for small businesses. That's our
compact. Everywhere we go, Meta
makes sure that we makes sure that we do
those things. But to answer your
question, Chamath, I don't think that
our industry has done a good job
communicating. Just just flat out. We
have to do a better job. But before you
can communicate anything, you've
actually got to be meaningful and have
real impact. And so we've started with
the premise that we want to be the best
actor and the best partner possible. And
now having frankly the impact that we
see in Louisiana, we're very proud of
the impact we're having in Texas and
Ohio, but I think we have to tell these
stories more. And I know you're alluding
to where is this information coming
from.
You know, I was just with
Chairman Cotton and Vice Chairman Mark
Warner in the Intelligence Committees.
You know, they do believe they have
evidence that our adversaries are trying
to gin this up. I can't comment on that,
but what I can tell you is if you wanted
to stop America right now, what would
you do? This is exactly what you would
try to do. If you were any of our
adversaries, you would want us to stop
building data centers in the United
States so that we could you know, we we
would not be on a path to being AI
dominant in the world. This is what you
would do. So whether they're doing it or
not, this is definitely an approach you
would take. And I I actually said to
them very respectfully, these are great
jobs, and the communities that want the
jobs, want the teacher bonuses, want
these investments should be allowed to
have them, and those that don't should
opt out, but we certainly don't want uh
our companies our my company and our
peers to start thinking about building
data centers
>> And it's so easy to debunk these issues.
The water one is the one that's just
confounding that
confounding that that narrative keeps
staying alive. I think you did an
amazing job.
>> X of this woman with this bottle of
dirty water that she trucks around, and
and you're just like
There's there's no there's no
>> what I you know what I love? I love that
it's a federated republic that the
founders designed, and some states are
going to win, some states are going to
be idiots, and they're going to lose,
and you know, you guys are going to have
this incredible economic advantage.
>> Uh yeah, I do want to add to to Dina's
point as well. Just as the teachers are
calling Sheldon to consider going to his
parish to teach, the minute that got
announced um that y'all were giving
$50,000 bonuses, I can't tell you how
many leaders of rural parishes in
Louisiana called me and said,
"Secretary, do do y'all have any who are
considering our parish? Please bring one
here." So so the global narrative is not
happening in Louisiana. I frankly I
don't believe it's happening everywhere
the way the propaganda says.
>> you from across the country like other
states saying, "Is this real? How did
this work?" And starting to kind of lean
in and see if they can
participate?
>> So historically, one of the challenges
we've had as a rural school system is
that our best and our brightest will
they'll they'll they'll do exceptionally
well in school. They may even go to our
local universities, but when they leave,
I have a good idea in my head that
they're not coming back to Richland
Parish because we can't offer a jobs
that that attract them. So they they
leave, and they go to other states, and
they go to other cities. And now we're
able to to to write our own narrative
that if you want to leave and go, you
can, but you don't have to.
We have opportunity here for you here in
Richland Parish. You have the ability to
stay here to raise your family, and I
think it's changing the narrative in our
parish.
>> Well, Deena, I know you've got another
video for us to watch also on um how do
we get more workers
to come and participate in this growing
economy. Um while we watch that, why
don't we thank Susan and Sheldon for
joining us. Thank you both for being
here. Thank you so much.
>> [applause]
[music]
>> Thank you so much. Appreciate you.
>> [music]
>> Very much appreciate you coming out.
Thank you so much.
>> I've always wanted to do something big.
I know that this is the program [music]
that I need to be in in order to
discover that.
>> In order for a lot of technology to
advance, we need the infrastructure.
Meta is blessing these guys with the
opportunity to be a part of that, to
help lay foundation for the future.
>> You can come into the program with no
prior experience. [music]
After you finish your four weeks here,
be able to go into the workforce.
>> [music]
>> I'm grateful for this opportunity. I'm
excited to actually get to do the work.
>> To have a group of students who [music]
are taking the opportunity serious and
are doing it with passion, that means
everything.
>> Once they're able [music] to finish our
course, there's so many different paths
that they can take.
>> The more that we learn and establish
this workforce, the more we can impact
future generations.
>> I feel like it will change the world.
I'm ready to work.
>> [music]
[applause]
>> You were telling me a story about like a
posting for fiber optic technician. Can
you just tell that story cuz I think
it's incredible?
>> So, um even in our site in Louisiana,
one of the issues is that we just can't
find enough workers. And you really need
a set of obviously welders and pipe
fitters and construction workers,
electricians. Uh but there's something
that every data center site really
needs, fiber technicians, the people
that just actually lay and cut the
fiber. And we just could not find enough
people. And so, we just made a
curriculum and we partnered with a few
people, CBRE and others. And uh we
realized that this program just didn't
exist. So, we decided if you can do it
for fiber technicians, why not go
beyond? It's a five-week fast-track
training program where you get all of
your safety training, you get uh
designated something called job site
ready, so you can get the job. We at
Meta guarantee you a job if you graduate
on one of our data center sites. And you
have that certification with you,
whether you want to stay at our site or
elsewhere. And the missing piece is that
while there are, as David Sax has said
over and over again, there are 500,000
open jobs for these uh roles over the
next couple of years, but there is this
gap between people actually getting
those jobs. And it's because it turns
out if you're a waitress, or you're an
Uber driver, or you are a home health
care worker, you live paycheck to
paycheck. You cannot afford to take that
time time off unpaid. The training is
weirdly very expensive, OSHA training
and things like that. And what if you do
that and you don't get a job? So, we
launched America's Workforce Academy. Uh
we launched it, I don't know, four
months ago. 40,000 Americans applied.
We've graduated 250 people. And we have
a 90% retention rate. So, people that
are getting into these contractor jobs
uh on our data center sites, um you can
see they've learned a new trade, they've
left behind a job that wasn't as
fulfilling, and that of course every
company that's hiring them um is just
thrilled. It's also something that's
interesting, David, that you you I
talked about, which is we
um, have partners across the board in
this program. We called we didn't put
Meta in the name because we are so
excited to be working with other
companies that are interested in
recruiting these workers as well.
Um, but we're working with the unions.
Sean McGarvey, uh, the head of the
trades, NABTU, um, is a friend and we
made a great partnership with him.
They're Some of those workers are on
union sites, some are non-union, but an
interesting voice that has emerged in
this debate is the unions. The union
leadership now is saying, "We want to be
anti the anti-data center backlash."
These are our jobs. These are for our
people. And so they actually put out,
even before the midterms,
um, a note saying they are only going to
support candidates that support data
centers.
>> How much, uh, balance
>> [applause]
>> A big change.
How much balance sheet capital does it
take to get this thing off the ground?
And do you see the other majors, the big
eight, kind of joining forces and having
this new educational track kind of
become a de facto standard in America?
>> You know, all of us are working on this.
In fact, I just talked to Ruth Porat at
Google. She's done an incredible job,
um, on workforce. And she's actually
brought together, uh, we're we're going
to join this alliance. Larry Fink at
BlackRock has joined the alliance. She's
bringing together other companies. You
know, we we might, uh, you know, might
compete on models and products, but we
don't want to compete on people. We we,
as an industry, I think are doing this
part well, where we're really working
together because anybody that gets
trained to work on a Meta data center
site can certainly go to a Google site
or a Microsoft site. And so this is a
place where we've really come together.
>> How do you How do you expand the
capacity? So there's 40,000 that
applied, but you picked 400. That's
39,600 that
>> Yeah, and and and we started four months
ago, and now, uh, we're literally
getting calls from Mary Barra at GM. I'd
like a thousand employees. You know,
once you have the curriculum and the
certification and the partners to
deliver it, uh, you can do these
everywhere. We're doing them in
community colleges, VFW halls. In that
particular program, you actually have to
have a site that's kind of like a model
data center so that you can show how to
train the fiber technicians, but we're
working with the Association of Builders
and Contractors. They have, you know,
thousands and thousands of of places
across the country where they operate.
>> why why is it so expensive outside of
you guys basically backstopping this?
To get something like job site ready and
OSHA awareness. I mean, this should seem
like you go online and
>> I think the thing that we unlocked is
that we actually pay during the training
what you would get if you are already in
the job. It used to be that there's a
very low fee or an apprentice fee for so
long that it wasn't, you know, it wasn't
the full pay payment of the job. And so
we do that from the beginning. And then
of course these jobs, I mean, David and
I've been in Pittsburgh with with some
of these workers. And you know, these
are jobs Welders make 100, 120,000
dollars a year in Pittsburgh. That is
meaningful, great work. And I think the
unlock that we're very proud of with
this program is that there just wasn't a
clear and fast path to getting on the
job site and to having a guaranteed job.
>> great that you have these jobs because
with AI progressing so quickly, these
developers are going to need something
to do. And so I think they can segue
into electrician jobs. I'm kidding
obviously.
But absolutely fantastic work on the
data centers. Fully supported. Great job
on the meta glasses.
>> [clears throat]
>> Amazing and and this effort
>> Where are your meta glasses, Jason? I
gave you such a
>> They're right here in the bag. Right in
my backpack. They're They're No, they're
actually super impressive. And this
effort is
>> This effort is truly impressive. But you
said you wanted me to do a fastball or
two.
And you you didn't want it to be
>> didn't say that, Jake Hall.
>> She literally asked me for at least one
one fastball. Uh so we'll just keep it
on softball.
>> Softball question. ask a question,
please please come back.
>> Yes, you know what, Jason?
>> No, no, no. We can just go We'll go
softballs. The boys prefer softballs.
No, well, I mean, it's
We We have Meta here and you just paid
the largest settlement in second only to
the tobacco industry
and just ahead of BP oil.
Two of the biggest disasters this
country ever faced and
this one is particularly tough.
>> And they wonder why they call him fake
news.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh no, I I I
>> Numbers are wrong.
>> I'm happy to talk about the Meta glasses
if you prefer.
>> I'm so glad Actually, seriously, I'm so
>> Go read your effective altruism.
>> I'm actually really glad you asked me
about it because
>> Yeah, well, no, let me finish the
question. You You may not be.
Um so
uh I'm going to lean in now, so to
speak.
Um
>> [laughter]
>> The The real, I think, challenge a lot
of us have with Facebook as an
organization and these are amazing. The
videos are super inspiring and well
produced, but you guys really did
damage, significant damage to children.
You knew that these products were too
addicting
and the philosophy of the company
from the beginning when Chamath was
there, "Hey, move fast, break things.
Let's go super fast." My My My sincere
question is how has the culture changed
inside of Facebook and you're making a
new series of potentially more addicting
products with character-based AI
companions, with Muse as a product. So,
I'm curious, what's changed in the
organization and what did you learn from
that record-setting fine and something
that is you could have done a lot better
on.
>> Um well, I totally disagree with
basically every single premise in your
question.
>> [laughter]
>> So,
the $17 settlement says otherwise.
>> get to speak or are you done with your
10-minute question? Um okay, I totally
disagree with the premise of that.
>> I see.
>> [applause]
>> I've only been there 8 months. I was on
the board for a and I can tell you cuz I
work with these people every day. They
are really, really focused on ensuring
that parents are empowered, teens are
supported, and I couldn't be actually
more proud of the agreement that we just
we just made. We made it with 52
bipartisan attorneys general across the
United States and the territories. We
are now setting industry standards.
We agreed that if your state signed on
with us that children under 18, not 16,
can only be on our platform for 2 hours
a day. The app shuts off after that and
it completely shops shuts off at night.
There are no notifications during the
school day at all of any kind. And
frankly, parents have way more
supervision now.
Many, many ways that they can decide
what their kids are on how long they're
on and what they're seeing. And I think
that we're proud of that because if
others in our peer group joined, this
could be pretty historic and
game-changing. And Jason, I'm a mom of
six daughters. So this is really
personal to me. I watched them grow up
in this in this generation. And I feel
that, you know, we really can actually
find a way to come together.
The reason your numbers were wrong on
the settlement is because we actually
agreed to give an additional $5 million
and to go down to only 1 hour of use on
our platform if YouTube, TikTok, and
Snap join us. Because as we know,
>> [applause]
>> as we know, people leave one set of apps
and go to another. But wouldn't it be
pretty amazing in America if
children under 18 could only be on apps
for an hour a day, shut off at night,
and I don't I just think that's what
>> Yes. 100% yes.
>> Thank you.
>> [applause]
>> Do you think Do you think it should be
universal, Chamath, or do you think it
should be controlled by the parent? Like
give the parent basic
>> it is controlled. What's your What's
your view?
>> Well, it is Meaning Meaning, obviously,
a parent can override it. But our app
actually just does turn off.
>> see.
>> Yeah.
>> Obviously, a parent. It's funny. I was
in Texas this weekend at the Texas Ohio
State game. You
>> [laughter]
>> my alma mater. And um and it was really
funny. I had so many uh people come up
to me and say, "You know you you know
this turning off cuz it it's literally
happening. Turning off Instagram is
hurting college college recruiting
football recruiting." I'm like, "What?
What are you talking about?" In Texas,
we put all of our kids videos on
Instagram and they get recruited. So, it
is interesting. I said, "Well, we live
in America. That's up to you. If you can
decide as a parent if you want to do
more, but it does actually shut off and
a parent has to override that."
>> I I think I think it's great.
Incredible. I remember just being with
my kids at the dinner table and my son
was trying to show me something and he
had hit the limit. Just turned off and
there's nothing and I was like, "This is
fantastic."
>> did you do like you're like leave it
off? Like
>> What What's that?
>> You're like just leave it off. You don't
care.
>> The reason is as a parent, it's
whack-a-mole.
>> Yeah.
>> Because
the content is syndicated across all
these platforms. And that's why what
you're saying is so right.
When my son when my kids my five kids go
to school,
they interact with YouTube as their
primary
outside of school mechanism because so
much of the school content and
educational content is there. So, even
if you shut off shorts and Instagram,
they pop up over here. So, it is this
whack-a-mole problem for parents and you
you it's a full-time job to manage it.
And so, if there is
effectively like a labeling and like,
you know, a decision on governance by
these companies, it's deeply helpful for
all of us that have jobs or trying to
live a life and raise kids normally so
they don't become zombies.
>> Zack, you're very active managing your
kids' mobile phone usage.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, how many do you have?
>> Look, I um
I I think the new defaults probably are
better. I mean, just thinking about my
kids' usage. Yeah, it'd be nice if it
turned off after, you know, an hour or
two.
Um so, yeah, look, I think that's that's
an improvement. I I do have to sort of
defend Meta because I do think that
there was a little bit of a ridiculous
pile on um where you know the company's
getting sued by adults who are blaming
the use of this completely voluntary
product. No one's forcing you to use any
of these social network products and
then something goes wrong in their life
that has many causes and then they're
suing meta and winning big judgments and
then the state AGs get in on the act and
all [clears throat] the trial lawyers
>> And the trial lawyers got half the money
I thought.
>> Yeah. So so let's acknowledge that there
is a little bit of a shakedown going on
here as well. I mean let's face it that
that is kind of how the American court
system works. But look I think that they
have reached a resolution that I think
is net beneficial and I like the new
defaults and ultimately this is about
parental control. You know parents
should choose
what you know and how what apps their
kids use and for how long. It should not
be the government doing that. It should
be the parents.
>> Yeah. [applause] Tina can you
>> just make it as easy as possible for the
parents to do it. And in my view the
only reason to do these new defaults is
because the whack-a-mole problem. It is
sometimes difficult
>> It's impossible to like figure out how
to control this stuff. I'm glad we're
having this discussion. Um I I think the
issue for me has been
the industry got very addicted to
gamification and designing products to
be addicting and increasing time spent
on app was in fact internally what
Facebook was focused on.
>> The challenge is you know it you can be
too good at something and I think
Facebook along with YouTube and their
algorithm were just too good at
addicting people to it whether they're
adults or kids and I will commend you
even if it was late as an organization
in doing the right thing now and then
leading the other organizations to do
the right thing.
>> Let me build on what you're saying with
a statement. Um and we Satya talked
about this. I think Jensen will talk
about it. Elon will talk about it but we
are you're going to hear this word RSI
over and over over the over the next 18
months, recursive self-improvement,
which is this idea that if you define a
function, a reward function for an AI
and let it go, it's going to
self-improve. So, to your point, Jason,
anything, whether it's, you know, World
of Warcraft or Angry Birds or whatever
app, you put it into an RSI loop and you
have the reward function being time,
they all these apps will proliferate.
Microsoft Word will keep you there for 9
hours if it can. So,
if unless companies make a decision like
you guys to say, "Here's a threshold and
beyond this threshold, we're just going
to turn it off." It's going to be kind
of turtles all the way
>> Yeah, this is what my point is, how does
it inform product decisions going
forward? You got this incredible new
product, Muse. You're you're you're in
the mix on the bots. Um but again, I
think the leadership and challenging the
other organizations is what I will give
you kudos for.
>> You know, I don't want to speculate
>> to I want to talk about this this this
this addiction thing as it relates to
the product that we all tried on
backstage. We all put on a meta glass.
And I'd never um I've never had the
product before.
What is the the repeated use case of
that product, you think? Like, what is
it that gets people cuz, you know, yeah,
the glasses, sorry. Yeah, so like, I
remember when Google had the goggles and
then Apple had VR and everyone's had an
effort at putting something on your face
and none of them have stickiness.
They're all like really interesting
novelty experiences and then your usage
tapers off and you kind of put it in the
drawer and it's like a cool tech relic.
>> Well, they're very stylish.
>> Yeah.
>> These are the Kylie Jenners.
Um no, actually, we are so excited about
this as a product. Um the the engineers
have been working on this for 10 years.
Um you make a good point that if people
don't look good in them and they're not
stylish, they're not going to put them
on. But uh you know, billions of people
wear glasses, whether they're to see uh
or obviously sunglasses. And we're
really excited about the features. You
can obviously listen to music. Uh the
only way I listen to All In every week
is wearing my Meta glasses as I'm
walking or working out. Uh they actually
have the incredible speaker, and so your
your phone calls are perfect. Uh and now
we have a couple of features we're
really excited about, conversation
focus. So, when Chamath is uh you know,
at dinner with his beautiful wife, and
he actually wants to hear her, if he
looks at her, all the noise uh it goes
away except her voice, which is pretty
cool. Um and then translation.
>> That's great.
>> Translation as well.
>> I do the opposite when I'm
>> Chamath, it's interesting. Tina, it's
interesting you bring this up, Tina.
>> Right.
>> Chamath was just telling me
>> I talked to you. I'd like to hear more
of that.
>> Chamath was just telling me he got the
new Apple AirPods 5 specifically because
of wife canceling noise.
>> oppo- the opposite. I want the opposite
feature.
>> You can actually tune in, but
>> Let me tell you why you're wrong and I'm
right. Okay, thanks.
>> [laughter]
>> But the other way I see with these
products, you're you know, you're you're
you're damned if you do and damned if
you don't in the sense that if you
design it poorly, no one's going to want
to use it. If you design it really well,
and it's a big success, a bunch of
trawlers are going to say it was
addictive, and then you get sued for
that.
>> So true.
>> Tina, can you
I sorry, I just wanted to move to AI for
a second before
>> No, I want to finish on this. So, like
So, but but but it has this kind of
recurrent use case built into it at this
point. Is that Cuz I really want to
understand if this
>> There's the reason so many people are
are working I mean, all of our peers are
working on wearables cuz I do think
people
want to be part of the world. They
actually don't want to be holding boxes
walking around. They actually really
want to be able to talk to their family,
take a picture, take a video, um listen
to music, and it be hands-free. We have
Oakleys uh that are really, really cool
for um extreme sports. So, the use cases
are just everyday life. And I think
you're going to show a video. The thing
that surprised us was one use case that
we hadn't anticipated, and that uh blind
veterans.
Um actually, somebody uh was joking with
me. They said, um "How are you getting
blind people to wear glasses? That
doesn't make sense to me. But can we
show this video?
>> It is such [music] an honor to be here.
We're in Austin, Texas at a VFW hall
where Meta mates are sitting down
[music] with amazing men and women who
served our country and who lost their
eyesight. They have just been telling us
they feel like they're getting [music]
their independence back and we're so
proud to be giving them Meta glasses.
>> I took them to church.
>> [music]
>> They have the scriptures on the screen
in front. I've never been able to read
that. But I asked Meta [music] and it
read it word for word for me.
>> Seeing these extraordinary servicemen
and women, all we've been saying is
thank you. Thank you. We don't have
America without all of them. And as a
big surprise, we are about to introduce
[music] them to Chris Stapleton.
>> I'm honored to come by and say thank you
for your service. I'm so grateful for
you.
>> Chris Stapleton's the best.
>> He He came and joined us. It was
actually on 9/11 and just a couple days
ago. And what we learned is that
a group of blind veterans from the
organization that that supports them
came and actually worked with the Meta
engineers and designed specific
features. And it just turns out
obviously the glasses can see for you
and read read to you. One of the
gentlemen I was sitting next to put the
glasses on and he said, "Hey Meta, call
John."
And I was sitting there I couldn't hear
obviously what he was hearing and he
just started sobbing. And I said, "Is
everything okay, sir?" He said, "That's
the first time I've ever called my son
on my own independently."
>> Wow.
>> So we're seeing these kinds of use cases
of course that we're incredibly proud
of.
>> I guess AI AI creates the unlock for the
glass form factor. That makes a lot of
sense. I cuz
>> Is that the form factor that you think
kind of gets AI in a prevalent way for
most people in the world is the glasses
form factor or is there something else
you think?
>> I'm I'm sure there'll be many products.
I mean I I think what I have learned
from our team
is that you know, glasses are a thing.
People wear glasses and it's something
that you know, many many people they're
affordable. And people obviously we
really worked hard. Mark was very
focused not just on the design but the
weight of it. So, takes a lot to put the
technology in here and to still keep it
stylish and and lightweight.
>> you're a that's an already owner of
Ray-Ban, no?
>> Yes.
>> Or of Luxottica of the of the broad
company.
>> our partner. Yeah, we have an exclusive
with
>> I think that's why people should
reconsider these, you know, as a product
category cuz I've had them since Google
Glass and the battery never worked. They
were too bulky. You look like a dork in
them. And now the battery works and
because you can control them, you know,
not with Siri which is still kind of
broken, but this actually works and when
you're with your kids and you want to
take videos when you're skiing or you
want to take pictures, it actually
you know, putting a phone between you is
is much more intrusive. So, I think this
actually brings you into the real world
and the translation feature is also very
slick. So, when you go to Japan or you
go somewhere and they're talking to you
in another language, it can actually
translate or if you see a sign, boom,
just instant translation without taking
your phone out.
It's time for people to reconsider these
specifically for those reasons.
>> Yeah. Um
>> You've used them a long time though, so
you really know.
>> Yeah, the batteries the battery problem,
the fidelity, just they didn't work and
now it does. Yeah, so.
>> Dina, just talking about the Dario's
essay this weekend, there was a report
but it was unverified that Zuck said
something to the effect of we need to go
as fast as we can.
Um I don't know if that was kind of
misinformation. No, no, that was like a
report that just hit Twitter at the same
time that Dario's or X when Dario sent
out. But just taking a step back
broadly, how did you process that essay
and the call for regulation or how are
you guys thinking about this?
>> Sure.
Well, first I really agree with a lot of
what Satya said. I mean, the the the
premise, the starting point is that
safety is paramount and that is
something that Mark talks about all the
time. I watch
daily how he and Alex Waing and Nat
Friedman who run our lab think about it
and they're in a whole team of people
exist to think about the safety of the
models
and I and I think that you know they're
very legitimate questions around that. I
think the difference is that
Mark just has a very different view and
I think that view is based on 20 years
of a business model of empowering and
connecting people and that 3.6 billion
people are on our platform every single
day. 200 million small business owners
operate their business every single day
and so his belief is that the more you
distribute this technology the more
people that have super intelligence and
are able to reach their potential are
able to have access to education and
health care that they could have never
imagined before learning that they could
have never achieved before is not only
better for each of those individuals but
it's better for society as a whole so he
fundamentally just believes when he
wrote in his piece the future is for
everyone that the democratization of
artificial intelligence will actually
lead to a more stable society. That is
just a fundamental belief that he has
and I think that
the thing that he thinks about is so
then what is his role what is our role
and I think we were extremely proud to
have the very first American open source
model just a few weeks ago.
>> Well Dina you've got a lot on your
plate. We really appreciate you taking
the time to come and join us today. We
covered a lot. It was awesome. Thank you
for being here.
>> Thank you guys so much.
>> [applause]
>> Thank you. We're going to walk up.
That was great.
>> [music]